Hello friends, welcome to our
YouTube channel. I hope you all are
healthy and at home. Today we are going to talk about
car insurance. Now
what can be interesting in car insurance.
You all know that there are different types of car
insurance - Road,
Comprehensive and Third Party. But today
we are going to talk about this insurance. Do
n't skip the video at all. Watch it completely.
I will put all the links of the content in the description.
You are already seeing it along with the video.
Whatever information is related to the sites is
coming on your video. There is
an article in Economic Times on 29th April in
which it has been
told about drive insurance which is being brought by Bhartiya Raksha in
collaboration with policybazaar.com. In this,
you have to pay the insurance according to the number of kilometers you drive the car.
There are three slabs in it - 25
kilometers, 5,000 kilometers and 7500
kilometers. Now you people have to decide first
how much your car runs.
Accordingly, you can take its insurance cover.
This is beneficial for those people
who have two or three vehicles
and they use the vehicle less or use it in the city, then
those people will not have to pay the full amount,
they will get a discount
because they drive less. In this,
according to these three slabs, you people have to choose the one
which is suitable for you and
accordingly you have to pay for it, so this is a
very good insurance cover and you are going to save a lot of
money in it.
ICICI number also has a separate insurance
scheme for size and happiness you
used. In this, there are three things on how you
drive, per used and single donor multiple
vehicle. According to this, they will see
how you drive and according to that,
if they feel that your driving
skills are good, then it is possible that you will get a
discount on it. In the same opinion, there is an
option of single donor multiple option in which those who have two or three
vehicles which are registered in the same name, then
they are also going to get an offer which is their time and for all three
vehicles, they will get a
discount in this.  You will get it at an
amazing price. They will monitor
your car by installing a system
on the speedometer so that you do
not tamper with the kilometers and they
will monitor how much your car has run. Please
like, share and subscribe to the video through live streaming.
Thank you.